Guide to the Robert Giard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2005 Acquisition, 1972-2002; 1; 50.06; (270 boxes)
  - Oversize Photographs (16" x 20")
    - Gay and Lesbian Writers
      - Male
        - Gurganus, Allan, 1989 April (Box 213)
          GLW# 0578
        - Gurganus, Allan, 1989 April (Box 213)
          GLW# 0579
        - Halperin, David M., 1992 March (Box 213)
          GLW# 0038
        - Hamilton, Ralph, 1988 July (Box 213)
          GLW# 0310
        - Hansen, Joseph, 1994 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0096
        - Harris, E. Lynn, 2000 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0208
        - Hay, Harry, 1989 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0693
        - Helbing, Terry, 1992 March (Box 213)
          GLW# 0036
        - Hemphill, Essex, at the Beams, 1991 May (Box 213)
          GLW# 0013
        - Hine, Daryl, 1993 June (Box 213)
          GLW# 0455
        - Hirsch, Michael, 1988 December (Box 213)
          GLW# 0323a
        - Hoffman, William, 1985 August (Box 213)
          GLW# 0347
        - Hoffman, William, 1985 August (Box 213)
          GLW# 0348
        - Holloran, Andrew, (Eric Garber), 1985 November (Box 213)
          GLW# 0355
        - Holsclaw, Douglas, at the Theater Rhinocerous, 1999 January (Box 213)
          GLW# 0182
        - Horowitz, Gene, 1986 August (Box 213)
          GLW# 0691
        - Howard, Richard, 1986 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0362
        - Howard, Richard, 1986 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0363
        - Howard, Richard, 1986 February (Box 213)
          GLW# 0364
        - Huston, Bo, 1992 October (Box 214)
          GLW# 0422
        - Indiana, Gary, 1989 November (Box 214)
          GLW# 0617
        - Innaurato, Albert, 1988 April (Box 214)
          GLW# 0702
        - Jess, 1996 January (Box 214)
          GLW# 0662
        - Jesurum, John, 1999 November (Box 214)
          GLW# 0206
        - Jones, Dorr(win) "Buck", 2000 July (Box 214)
          GLW# 0219a
        - Jones, Cleve at the Quilt Center/ The Names Project, 1988 January (Box 214)
          GLW# 0265
        - Judell, Brandon, 1987 August (Box 214)
          GLW# 0120
        - Kalstone, David, Looking at Chris, 1985 December (Box 214)
          GLW# 0349
        - Kalstone, David, 1985 December (Box 214)
          GLW# 0350
        - Kameny, Franklin, 1991 March (Box 214)
          GLW# 0478a
        - Kantrowitz, Arnie, 1987 April (Box 214)
          GLW# 0380
        - Karcher, Roland M., 2001 August (Box 214)
          GLW# 0234
        - Katz, Jonathan Ned, 1988 June (Box 214)
          GLW# 0298a
        - Kennedy, Hubert, 1994 January (Box 214)
          GLW# 0074
        - Kenny, Maurice, 1992 August (Box 214)
          GLW# 0049
        - Kepner, Jim, 1992 March (Box 214)
          GLW# 0041
        - Kertess, Klaus, 2000 June (Box 214)
          GLW# 0211
        - Kertess, Klaus, 2000 June (Box 214)
          GLW# 0212
        - Kertess, Klaus, 2000 June (Box 214)
          GLW# 0213
        - Kight, Morris, 1996 January (Box 214)
          GLW# 0668a
        - Kikel, Rudy, 1987 July (Box 215)
          GLW# 0099
        - Killian, Kevin, 19888 January (Box 215)
          GLW# 0252
        - Killian, Kevin, 1988 January (Box 215)
          GLW# 0254
        - Klein, Michael, 1988 March (Box 215)
          GLW# 0291
        - Kleinberg, Seymour, 1987 April (Box 215)
          GLW# 0382
        - Kleinberg, Seymour, Man with Oriental Sculpture, 1981 May (Box 215)
          GLW# 0698
        - Koestenbaum, Wayne, 1992 March (Box 215)
          GLW# 0037a
        - Kondoleon, Harry, 1992 April (Box 215)
          GLW# 0043
        - Kondoleon, Harry, 1992 April (Box 215)
          GLW# 0162
        - Kondoleon, Harry, 1992 April (Box 215)
          GLW# 0163
        - Kopkind, Andrew, 1993 May (Box 215)
          GLW# 0443
        - Kramer, Larry with Molly, 1989 December (Box 215)
          GLW# 0618b
        - Kushner, Tony with Karl Marx Pillows, 1995 March (Box 215)
          GLW# 0643a
        - Labonte, Richard at Different Light, 1989 January (Box 215)
          GLW# 0563
        - Lambe, Ron, 1991 March (Box 215)
          GLW# 0496
        - Lassell, Michael, 1988 January (Box 215)
          GLW# 0281a
        - Leavitt, David, 1987 February (Box 215)
          GLW# 0533
        - Leavitt, David, 1987 February (Box 215)
          GLW# 0534
        - Legg, Dorr, at the One Institute, 1994 January (Box 215)
          GLW# 0387a
        - Leitsch, Dick, 1999 February (Box 215)
          GLW# 0190
        - Leventhal, Stan, 1987 August (Box 215)
          GLW# 0097
        - Leyland, Winston, 1994 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0180
        - Leyland, Winston, 1994 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0377
        - Liu, Timothy at the Poetry Society Library, 1993 November (Box 216)
          GLW# 0072
        - Long, Robert, 1992 September (Box 216)
          GLW# 0054a
        - Lucas, Don, 1999 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0186
        - Lucas, Craig, 1989 December (Box 216)
          GLW# 0619
        - Manley, Joey, 1992 February (Box 216)
          GLW# 0029
        - Manrique, Jaime, 1992 July (Box 216)
          GLW# 0056
        - Mariah, Paul at Small Press Traffic, 1988 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0256
        - Martin, Robert K., 1992 April (Box 216)
          GLW# 0045
        - Mass, Lawrence, 1987 April (Box 216)
          GLW# 0381
        - Maupin, Armistead, 1989 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0565e
        - McCauley, Steven, 1987 July (Box 216)
          GLW# 0101
        - McClatchy, J.D., 1987 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0520
        - McClatchy, J.D., 1987 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0521
        - McCourt, James, 1987 December (Box 216)
          GLW# 0134
        - McDonald, Boyd, 1987 August (Box 216)
          GLW# 0114
        - McNally, Terrence, 1986 September (Box 216)
          GLW# 0504
        - McNally, Terrence, 1986 September (Box 216)
          GLW# 0505a
        - McVay, Daniel, 1989 January (Box 216)
          GLW# 0597
        - Mead, Taylor, 1991 April (Box 217)
          GLW# 0002
        - Merla, Patrick, 1989 August (Box 217)
          GLW# 0612
        - Merlis, Mark, 1999 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0183
        - Merrill, Michael, 1988 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0276
        - Miller, Neil, 1987 July (Box 217)
          GLW# 0111
        - Milne, Bob, 2000 April (Box 217)
          GLW# 0223
        - Mitchell, Larry, 1989 August (Box 217)
          GLW# 0609
        - Mitzel, John, 1987 September (Box 217)
          GLW# 0123
        - Mohr, Richard, 1993 June (Box 217)
          GLW# 0463
        - Monette, Paul, 1988 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0282
        - Monette, Paul with Dog, 1988 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0283
        - Money, John, 1991 March (Box 217)
          GLW# 0476
        - Mordden, Ethan, 1987 August (Box 217)
          GLW# 0392
        - Morse, Carl, 1987 August (Box 217)
          GLW# 0116
        - Nava, Michael, 1988 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0278
        - Navarre, Max, 1987 September (Box 217)
          GLW# 0100
        - Nichols, Jack, 1998 February (Box 217)
          GLW# 0683a
        - Nichols, Jack on Balcony, 1998 February (Box 217)
          GLW# 0684a
        - Norse, Harold, 1988 January (Box 217)
          GLW# 0257
        - O'Hara, Scott, 1993 July (Box 218)
          GLW# 0451a
        - O'Hara, Scott, 1993 July (Box 218)
          GLW# 0452a
        - Otero, Manuel Ramos, 1988 April (Box 218)
          GLW# 0287
        - Otero, Manuel Ramos, 1988 April (Box 218)
          GLW# 0288
        - Owen, Mark, 1988 December (Box 218)
          GLW# 0557
        - Peck, Dale, 1993 June (Box 218)
          GLW# 0446
        - Peck, Dale, 1993 June (Box 218)
          GLW# 0447
        - Peck, Dale, 1993 June (Box 218)
          GLW# 0448
        - Peters, Robert, 1988 January (Box 218)
          GLW# 0237
        - Phillips, Carl, 2000 August (Box 218)
          GLW# 0221
        - Picano, Felice, 1985 September (Box 218)
          GLW# 0346b
        - Pickett, James Carroll, 1988 November (Box 218)
          GLW# 0551
        - Pintauro, Joe, man in a Wicker Chair, 1980 August (Box 218)
          GLW# 0706
        - Pintauro, Joe, 1989 August (Box 218)
          GLW# 0611a
        - Plant, Richard, 1989 March (Box 218)
          GLW# 0602
        - Preston, John, 1988 July (Box 218)
          GLW# 0304
        - Puig, Manuel, 1979 (Box 218)
          GLW# 0209a
        - Purdy, James, 11/87 (Box 218)
          GLW# 0124
        - Reed, Paul, 1994 January (Box 218)
          GLW# 0076
        - Reed, Paul, with Tattoo, 1994 January (Box 218)
          GLW# 0169
        - Rist, Darrel Yates, 1986 November (Box 219)
          GLW# 0511
        - Rist, Darrel Yates, 1986 November (Box 219)
          GLW# 0512
        - Robinson, Harlow, 1988 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0279
        - Robinson, Colin, 1988 October (Box 219)
          GLW# 0550
        - Robinson, Harold McNeil, 1990 March (Box 219)
          GLW# 0624
        - Rodwell, Craig at the Oscar Wilde Bookstore, 1992 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0023
        - Rofes, Eric, 1988 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0286a
        - Rorem, Ned, 1987 April (Box 219)
          GLW# 0376
        - Rorem, Ned, 1987 April (Box 219)
          GLW# 0689
        - Roscoe, Will, 1994 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0384
        - Rowlands, Craig, 1990 June (Box 219)
          GLW# 0469
        - Russell, Paul, 1992 August (Box 219)
          GLW# 0057
        - Russo, Vito, 1987 March (Box 219)
          GLW# 0545
        - Russo, Vito, 1987 March (Box 219)
          GLW# 0546
        - Saint, Assotto (Yves Lubain), 1987 March (Box 219)
          GLW# 0530
        - Sarria, Jose, 1999 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0184a
        - Saslow, James, 1986 September (Box 219)
          GLW# 0373
        - Saslow, James, "La Saslova", 1986 September (Box 219)
          GLW# 0374
        - Schmidt, Paul, 1993 January (Box 219)
          GLW# 0427
        - Schneebaum, Tobias, 1991 December (Box 219)
          GLW# 0022
        - Schreiber, Ron, with Arm-Band for Lover, 1987 August (Box 219)
          GLW# 0122
        - Schuyler, James at the Chelsea Hotel, 1989 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0613
        - Schwartz, Lloyd, 1988 July (Box 220)
          GLW# 0308
        - Schwartz, Lloyd, 1988 July (Box 220)
          GLW# 0309
        - Shilts, Randy, 1989 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0574
        - Shilts, Randy, 1989 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0575
        - Shivley, Charles, 1987 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0128
        - Shivley, Charles, 1987 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0129
        - Shurin, Aaron, 1988 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0261
        - Silin, Jonathan, Man in an Arctic Cap, 1981 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0700
        - Simmons, Steve, 1989 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0573
        - Spanbauer, Tom, 1994 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0697
        - Stadler, Matthew, 1994 July (Box 220)
          GLW# 0340
        - Stambolian, George with Durer Self- Portrait, 1986 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0501
        - Stambolian, George, 1986 September (Box 220)
          GLW# 0502
        - Stambolian, George with a Durer Self Portrait, 1987 October (Box 220)
          GLW# 0690
        - Stambolian, George, 1987 May (Box 220)
          GLW# 0701
        - Steele, Tom, 1988 March (Box 220)
          GLW# 0290
        - Steward, Samuel (Phil Andros), 1988 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0275
        - Stuart, Rob (Box 220)
          GLW# 0715a
        - Tan, Joel B., 1996 January (Box 220)
          GLW# 0671
        - Tavel, Ronald, 1992 February (Box 221)
          GLW# 0031
        - Teske, Edmund, 1996 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0669
        - Teske, Edmund, 1996 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0670
        - Thompson, Mark, 1989 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0581
        - Thornton, Gene, Man in a T-Shirt, 1984 August (Box 221)
          GLW# 0687
        - Thornton, Gene, 1984 August (Box 221)
          GLW# 0688
        - Toibin, Colm, 2001 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0224
        - Trachtenberg, David, 1988 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0240
        - Tribute to Joe Beam (Box 221)
          GLW# 0005a
        - Trinidad, David, 1988 January (Box 221)
          GLW# 0277
        - Turnbaugh, Douglas, 1993 November (Box 221)
          GLW# 0073
        - Van Buskirk, Jim, at Library Reading Room, 2000 July (Box 221)
          GLW# 0216
        - Van Buskirk, Jim, at Library Reading Room, 2000 July (Box 221)
          GLW# 0218
        - Vining, Donald, 1991 November (Box 221)
          GLW# 0019
        - Virga, Vincent, 1987 December (Box 221)
          GLW# 0242
        - Von Praunheim, Rosa, 1987 December (Box 221)
          GLW# 0246
        - Von Praunheim, Rosa, 1987 December (Box 221)
          GLW# 0247
        - Watney, Simon, chez Bronski/Borawski, 1988 July (Box 221)
          GLW# 0313
        - Weinberg, Dr. George, 2000 November (Box 221)
          GLW# 0222
        - White, Marvin K., 2000 July (Box 221)
          GLW# 0220
        - White, Edmund, 1985 September (Box 222)
          GLW# 0342
        - White, Edmund, 1985 September (Box 222)
          GLW# 0343
        - Whitmore, George, at the World's Fair, 1987 January (Box 222)
          GLW# 0532
        - Wicker, Randy, at Uplift Lighting, 1991 June (Box 222)
          GLW# 0012a
        - Wicker, Randy, at Uplift Lighting, 1991 June (Box 222)
          GLW# 0105
        - Wieners, John, 1990 June (Box 222)
          GLW# 0467
        - Williams, Jonathan, 1991 March (Box 222)
          GLW# 0497
        - Wilson, Doric, 1991 October (Box 222)
          GLW# 0017
        - Wilson, Lanford with Dogs, 1986 October (Box 222)
          GLW# 0508
        - Wilson, Lanford with Dogs, 1986 October (Box 222)
          GLW# 0509
        - Wilson, Lanford, New Year's Day with Sweater from his Mother, 1986 October (Box 222)
          GLW# 0510
        - Wong, Norman, 1993 December (Box 222)
          GLW# 0060a
        - Woods, Donald, 1987 March (Box 222)
          GLW# 0531
        - Wright, Bil, 1990 February (Box 222)
          GLW# 0628
        - Yew, Chay, 1999 March (Box 222)
          GLW# 0195
        - Young, Allen, 1992 March (Box 222)
          GLW# 0030
        - Zane, Arnie, 1987 September (Box 222)
          GLW# 0202
        - Zane, Arnie, 1987 September (Box 222)
          GLW# 0203
      - Female
        - Abbott, Sidney, 1992 August (Box 223)
          GLW# 0175
        - Allen, Paula Gunn, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0266
        - Allen, Paula Gunn, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0267
        - Allen, Paula Gunn, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0269
        - Allison, Dorothy, 1987 September (Box 223)
          GLW# 0136
        - Andalzua, Gloria, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0263
        - Andalzua, Gloria, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0264
        - Anshaw, Carol, 1993 June (Box 223)
          GLW# 0460
        - Bannon, Ann, 1989 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0561
        - Bechdel, Allison, 1995 July (Box 223)
          GLW# 0650
        - Bellamy, Dodie, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0250
        - Bellamy, Dodie, 1988 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0251
        - Ben, Lisa, 1997 February (Box 223)
          GLW# 0673
        - Ben, Lisa, 1997 February (Box 223)
          GLW# 0674
        - Bereano, Nancy, 1989 May (Box 223)
          GLW# 0603
        - Birtha, Becky, 1991 May (Box 223)
          GLW# 0007
        - Bishop, Jacquie, 1988 September (Box 223)
          GLW# 0312a
        - Bradley, Marion Zimmer, 1994 January (Box 223)
          GLW# 0077a
        - Brant, Beth, 1990 March (Box 223)
          GLW# 0623
        - Brossard, Nicole, 1992 April (Box 223)
          GLW# 0047
        - Broumas, Olga, 1987 August (Box 224)
          GLW# 0092
        - Broumas, Olga, 1987 July (Box 224)
          GLW# 0145a
        - Broumas, Olga, 1987 July (Box 224)
          GLW# 0146
        - Brown, Rebecca, 1994 July (Box 224)
          GLW# 0397a
        - Bunch, Charlotte, 1990 April (Box 224)
          GLW# 0464
        - Cadden, Wendy, 1998 September (Box 224)
          GLW# 0181
        - Califia, Pat, 1996 January (Box 224)
          GLW# 0653
        - Cameron, Barbara, undated (Box 224)
          GLW# 0658
        - Castillo, Ana, 1989 January (Box 224)
          GLW# 0567
        - Chan, June, 1988 September (Box 224)
          GLW# 0319
        - Chrystos, 1994 August (Box 224)
          GLW# 0638
        - Chrystos, 1994 August (Box 224)
          GLW# 0640a
        - Clarke, Cheryl, 1987 August (Box 224)
          GLW# 0093a
        - Clausen, Jan, 1988 October (Box 224)
          GLW# 0322
        - Cook, Blanche Wiesen, 1993 September (Box 224)
          GLW# 0068
        - Cook, Blanche Wiesen, 1987 September (Box 224)
          GLW# 0140
        - Corrine, Tee, 1994 August (Box 224)
          GLW# 0409
        - Coss, Clare, 1987 September (Box 224)
          GLW# 0141a
        - DeLynn, Jane, 1991 November (Box 224)
          GLW# 0018a
        - Donnelly, Nisa, 1994 January (Box 224)
          GLW# 0083
        - Dworkin, Andrea, 1992 November (Box 225)
          GLW# 0424
        - Faderman, Lillian, 1994 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0078
        - Fornes, Maria Irene, 1990 February (Box 225)
          GLW# 0627
        - Forrest, Katherine V., 1989 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0584
        - Garden, Nancy, 1997 November (Box 225)
          GLW# 0680
        - Gardinier, Suzanne, 1994 June (Box 225)
          GLW# 0336
        - Gearhart, Sally, 1996 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0665
        - Gomez, Jewelle, 1987 May (Box 225)
          GLW# 0090
        - Goodman, Melinda, 1988 October (Box 225)
          GLW# 0316a
        - Grahn, Judy The Earring:... with Chris Brandenberger, 1988 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0259
        - Grahn, Judy, 1988 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0260
        - Grier, Barbara, 1989 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0600
        - Griffin, Susan, 1988 January (Box 225)
          GLW# 0262
        - Grumbach, Doris, 1991 March (Box 225)
          GLW# 0480
        - Hacker, Marilyn, 1987 September (Box 225)
          GLW# 0137
        - Hampton, Mabel, undated (Box 225)
          GLW# 0710a
        - Hampton, Mabel (eyes closed), undated (Box 225)
          GLW# 0711
        - Hampton, Mabel (looking up), undated (Box 225)
          GLW# 0707
        - Hampton, Mabel (lips open), undated (Box 225)
          GLW# 0708
        - Hampton, Mabel (smiling), undated (Box 225)
          GLW# 0709
        - Harjo, Joy, 1990 March (Box 226)
          GLW# 0632
        - Harjo, Joy, 1990 March (Box 226)
          GLW# 0633
        - Harris, Bertha, 1993 March (Box 226)
          GLW# 0436
        - Hughes, Holly, 1988 June (Box 226)
          GLW# 0292
        - Jay, Karla, 1991 June (Box 226)
          GLW# 0015
        - Kim, Willyce, 1989 January (Box 226)
          GLW# 0562
        - Klaitch, Dolores, 1986 October (Box 226)
          GLW# 0506
        - Klepfisz, Irena, 1987 May (Box 226)
          GLW# 0091
        - Kogan, Jane, 1980 (Box 226)
          GLW# 0713
        - Kogan, Jane, 1987 July (Box 226)
          GLW# 0390
        - Lapidus, Jacqueline, 1988 July (Box 226)
          GLW# 0314
        - Larkin, Joan, 1987 December (Box 226)
          GLW# 0243
        - Lorde, Audre, 1987 May (Box 226)
          GLW# 0085
        - Love, Barbara, 1994 May (Box 226)
          GLW# 0327
        - Lowe, Bia, 1989 January (Box 226)
          GLW# 0590
        - Lynch, Lee, 1994 August (Box 226)
          GLW# 0414
        - Lyon, Phyllis and Del Martin, 1989 January (Box 226)
          GLW# 0571
        - Martin, Del, 1989 January (Box 226)
          GLW# 0572
        - Martinac, Paula, 1991 December (Box 226)
          GLW# 0021
        - Mays, Raymina, 1991 March (Box 226)
          GLW# 0477
        - Meaker, Marijane, 2000 July (Box 227)
          GLW# 0215
        - Meigs, Mary, 1992 April (Box 227)
          GLW# 0046
        - Miller, Isabel, 1992 August (Box 227)
          GLW# 0164
        - Millett, Kate, 1987 November (Box 227)
          GLW# 0241
        - Moore, Honor, 1989 June (Box 227)
          GLW# 0604
        - Moraga, Cherrie, 1989 January (Box 227)
          GLW# 0566
        - Morgan, Robin, 1992 March (Box 227)
          GLW# 0028
        - Mountaingrove, Jean, 1994 August (Box 227)
          GLW# 0411
        - Myles, Eileen, 1988 March (Box 227)
          GLW# 0289a
        - Nestle, Joan at the Lesbian Herstory Archives, 1987 September (Box 227)
          GLW# 0132
        - Nestle, Joan, 1987 September (Box 227)
          GLW# 0133
        - Newton, Esther, 1990 April (Box 227)
          GLW# 0635
        - Olesko, Pat, 1990 August (Box 227)
          GLW# 0705
        - Pally, Marcia, 1988 June (Box 227)
          GLW# 0297
        - Parker, Peter, 1989 January (Box 227)
          GLW# 0576
        - Parkerson, Michelle, 1991 March (Box 227)
          GLW# 0491
        - Patton, Cindy, 1988 July (Box 227)
          GLW# 0302
        - de la Pena, Terri, 1994 January (Box 227)
          GLW# 0176
        - Porter, Veneita, 1988 July (Box 227)
          GLW# 0303
        - Pratt, Minnie Bruce, 1991 March (Box 227)
          GLW# 0479
        - Ramos, Juanita, 1988 June (Box 228)
          GLW# 0295a
        - Randall, Margaret, 1998 September (Box 228)
          GLW# 0200
        - Ranson, Rebecca, 1992 January (Box 228)
          GLW# 0027
        - Redmann, J. M., 1999 February (Box 228)
          GLW# 0034
        - Replansky II, Naomi, 1995 August (Box 228)
          GLW# 0651
        - Rich, Adrienne, 1987 April (Box 228)
          GLW# 0084
        - Rich, Adrienne, 2001 October (Box 228)
          GLW# 0232
        - Rich, Adrienne, 1987 April (Box 228)
          GLW# 0378
        - Rich, Adrienne, 1989 January (Box 228)
          GLW# 0559
        - Rivera, Silvia Rey, undated (Box 228)
          GLW# 0194
        - Robson, Ruthann, 1992 September (Box 228)
          GLW# 0418
        - Roma-Carmona, Mariana, 1988 September (Box 228)
          GLW# 0317
        - Rubin, Gayle, 1994 January (Box 228)
          GLW# 0161
        - Rule, Jane, 1994 August (Box 228)
          GLW# 0410
        - Rushin, Donna Kate, 1987 August (Box 228)
          GLW# 0121
        - Russ, Joanna, 1998 September (Box 228)
          GLW# 0152
        - Sam, Canyon, 1996 January (Box 228)
          GLW# 0654
        - Sapphire, 1988 June (Box 228)
          GLW# 0293
        - Sarton, May, 1994 June (Box 228)
          GLW# 0333
        - Schulman, Sarah, 1989 May (Box 228)
          GLW# 0580
        - Sears, Vickie, 1990 (Box 229)
          GLW# 0634
        - Shelley, Martha, undated (Box 229)
          GLW# 0656
        - Sherman, Susan, 1988 November (Box 229)
          GLW# 0552
        - Simo, Ana Maria, 1990 March (Box 229)
          GLW# 0622
        - Smith, Barbara, 1987 August (Box 229)
          GLW# 0094
        - Sneed, Pamela, 1992 June (Box 229)
          GLW# 0052
        - Speicher, Rita, 1988 July (Box 229)
          GLW# 0301
        - Teubal, Savina, 1988 January (Box 229)
          GLW# 0284
        - Thomas, Sherry, 1996 January (Box 229)
          GLW# 0659
        - Tilchen, Maida, 1988 July (Box 229)
          GLW# 0307
        - Tribute to Joe Beam, undated (Box 229)
          GLW# 0006e
        - Trujillo, Carla, 1996 January (Box 229)
          GLW# 0657
        - Kitty, Tsui, 1988 January (Box 229)
          GLW# 0258
        - Ulrich, Barbara, 1987 May (Box 229)
          GLW# 0147
        - Ulrich, Barbara, 1987 May (Box 229)
          GLW# 0383a
        - Vaid, Urvashi, 1991 March (Box 229)
          GLW# 0485
        - Villaneuva, Chea, 1988 June (Box 229)